I feel much freer after the last one the
one I didn't want to do I just feel
there's more space inside of me I just
want to share that and also I had
another idea now I've lost it I'm sure I
can come up with something as I'm
looking because that seems to be what
I'm doing so idea number 91 I'm gonna
ten more and that I have to never have
ideas again that's ridiculous
nine more really is I don't remember I
don't look like the idea was I could I
think I already said this before and I
know there's problems with it
anyway a forward gene app an app that
tells you where food grows what food is
safe to eat when it's in season and more
importantly if you're gonna have that it
needs to be showing us how to be good
stewards so if it's shown for people
where that is it didn't show anyone else
there everyone only takes like a maximum
of 50% total and of course you have to
honor the indigenous people already live
there and possibly use that for for
their food but I am bored yeah with a
big societal discussion on whether
that's ethical and what that means
so that is Apple number 92